Guide to the Benjamin D. Paul Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2003-186
  - Audio interviews, some transcribed (Box 7)
    - A: Ben - Cult ch 5/3; B: Ben 5-10., 1 audiocasette(s) (Box 7, 24)
    - A: 2-27-91 Agapito, A only, transcribed 1-150 only., 1991; 1 audiocasette(s) (Box 7, 24)
    - A: Elena 2/7 (4)., 1 audiocasette(s) (Box 7, 24)
    - A: Felipe Chav. 4/10/00; B: Agustin Pop 4/11/00., 2000; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7, 24)
  - Ethnic art files (Box 8)
    Note: box 8 also contains 8 artist booklets, one being hardcover.
    - Postcards and mailing record (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Raf. Gz y Gz: Diary (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Art Ms (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Bunge/Sombol (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Gomez Davis, Alfredo (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - List of Painters: SP and SJ (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Comalapa: Linda Asturias and others (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Raf. Gz y Gz: comments, Janie (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Art, notes, and misc. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Interviews: P. Raf. by BDP and Joe J. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Chema Gz Cox: transcript (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Benjamin Gz. Ch: florid prose, curric. Vitae (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Vasquez Tema, Lorenzo Gz Chav. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Interview: Ant. Coche Ixtamer 1/93 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Interview: Matias by Joe J. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Interviews: Mariano, BDP '91 and '93, Joe J. ‘93 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Painters, misc. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Gz hermanos: clippings. Benjamin publicity (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Interview: Bartolo Q. Cruz (JJ) (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Interviews: Lencho Gz Mendoza, Lencho Gz Chav. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Mitchel, Nancy, "Why Do [Pueblo] Indians Make Art" (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Artists' data, misc. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Paintings and misc. 7-8/91 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Lorenzo Gz Ch (by Jose), "Lencho" ex tesorero, Victor Vasquez (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Ethic Art paper (empty) (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Jose J: Maya Art Exhibs: 1991-93 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Art – Misc. Jose copy on Juanelos, etc. (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Jose J. Corresp. Etc. exhibitions (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Jose J: SP, 5 motives S Jn 9'93 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - AES Ms: Artists (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Ethnic Art (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Cesar Arriola '91 tape (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Interviews: Ronaldo son of Marta? 12/25/94 and Ms. Juan Chav. Mendez 2/14/96 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - "Miscellaneous files to sort" – includes maps
    - Genealogies and Pamaxan swith (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Maps: Guate/Coffee belt (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Maps: Pamaxan, other, SP la Lag (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Maps: C. America (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Maps: S. Pedro, Panajachel (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Maps: SP la L/ Guate, etc. (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - SP notes, misc to re-sort (6/30/95) (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Guate 7/13-8/9 1995 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - For SP Ms: Misc. items 11/93 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Interviews '94, ‘95 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - In process: polling, educ. (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Take to P. Alto (8/95) (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Selected Barb's schedules 8/91, to Guate 7/95 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Misc. (educ. etc) to SP 7/95 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Interviews July ‘95: Felipe Chv. Ixt., J. Ant. Chav. P. (part), Santos Perez (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Clippings, not S Pedro (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Very Misc. July ‘95 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Interview: Santos Q. Peres (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - SP Diary/notes, escritas, ‘94-‘95 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - S. Pedro: 7/21-8/18/94 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Interviews y transcripciones: Raf/Chico Aug. ‘94 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Barb's sched's worksheets for 10/91 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Barb's schedules I (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Take to Guate July ‘95 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Take back Aug. ‘94 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - 1968 – orig. (more complete than carbons, but scarce?) (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Correspondence: Ben, Guat, summer 1973 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Lists, letters, minutes (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - 1973 Lois, 1974 Field Notes – copy! (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Misc: picked from old (1967+) misc. folder (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Interview: Demarest 1973, Migrants (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Correspondence 1975 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Transforming Witches: essay (to be) (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Building Plans, Lake Atitlan 1975 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - BD Paul, Corresp. 1968-69 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - 1956 copy 1 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - 1962 Lencho Excritos copy (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - 1962 June copy (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - 1962 July copy (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - S. Pedro field notes 1962 from Sterlings (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - 1964 field notes copy (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Guate. '64, some '65. Summer 1964: details concerning Paul's travel, etc. (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Field notes, 1968-75
    - 1975 Jan-March notes (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - SP field notes, misc and mixed (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - 1974 field notes, S. Pedro la Laguna, Bonesetter (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Field notes – 1956 copy 1 – In Crockers House
    - 1965 notes copy (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - In Crocker's Hse. 1965, letter to Ala. Suzie (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Files on coffee
    - Coffee notes, articles, letters, and papers (McDowell) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Coffee Misc. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Chas MacVean: coffee, also Kiki Abril (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Document: Coffee (2 pp), Oct. 1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Coffee in New Guinea (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Misc. articles, papers, photos, and interview notes (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Coffee: Corresp. Barb and Pablo (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Murray, Douglas L. "Pesticides and Nontraditional Agriculture…" (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - AID/ANACAFE, APECAN data (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Coffee: Corresp. Peggy Barlett, Brian Barke, etc. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Progress Report (3 pp) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Sandy Davis, corresp. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Coffee Misc. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Watanabe Chapter (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Coffee: Consultants – Watanabe, Locecky (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Betty Adams: Coffee (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Coffee: Ron Nigh pp and corr. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - B. D. Paul diaries, 1991-93
    - Diary 4/83, visit with Bill (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Notes/diary, 10/86, 23 pp. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - S. Pedro Misc., diary notes 1988, exchange rantes (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Diary, 2/13-3/5 1991, pp. 1-33 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Ag Diary 4/7/91, murdes, etc. (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Ag Pop – manuscript ?
    - Ag. Pup's Conversion transcripts, Mardo Pop (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Files from desk – correspondence, starting with Wilson
    - Notes, 1/30-2/11 1998 and some cullable misc. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - 1986 notes, duplicate (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Field notes, March 1986 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - SP 1985 interviews, duplicates (Xerox) (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - 1985 SP interviews, sequestros (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - SP 1983: I (pre SP), pp. 1-19 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - SP 1983: II, pp. 20-51 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - SP 1983: III (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Memo of San Pedro 4/83, hand-written (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - SP notes, 4/18-28/83, duplicates (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Tapes/Transcriptions, Jan. 1992, in process and antecedents (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Transcripts in progress, Jan. 28, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Transcriptions: Ant. Batz ('86,'88), Julio ('86), Tono Chv. ('88), Isaias Cc ('88), P. Alb Cuc ('91), Bart Q ('88), Luis Mz ('86), Chico Mendoza ('88), Vict. Tuch ('91), Bart Y ('91) (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Chema El Alto Trans, Erasma Pz, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Index: Archivo (fr. McCreedy) (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Goldin Mss and corresp. 1992 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - S. Pedro Misc. (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Ms Domingo Ga Ixmota trip to San Fran (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Brigit Helms '91, Xerox (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Inequality/Entrepreneur paper (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Ant. Max Ch. Ms 3/91 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Agapito trans. 2/91, Vicente Cumes trans. 1/93 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Wilson-Grau (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Wendy Weiss, ed. JLAm St. (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Watanabe/Abig. Adams, 11/96 AAA abstract, corresp. (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Victoria Sanford (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Lee Ann Ward (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Samol Sicay (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Nathaniel Tarn (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Rogoff: Chona Ms, Lib Comm. etc (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Prybot corresp. '97-11/98 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Mulhare, Eileen (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - M. Moors, corresp. (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Maya Edl Fdn, Susan Feinberg (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Lutz/Mesoamerica (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Little-Siebold, Christa (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Bob Laughlin (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Pat Krause/Behrhorst, etc. (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Joe Johnston (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Koizumi, Junji (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Kjell Enge, corrsp. (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Gonzaez/deguerrotypes, Dale Neighbors (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Nancie L. Gonzalez (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Elena Gz Cox (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Lucila Gz (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Chema Gz Cox (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Santos Garcia Gz (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Cotuc, Delfina (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Pablo Chavaj ay Petzey (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Chav., Pablo and Barb, (21. Nov. '88 add San Carlos students) (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Chav. Mendez, Pedo El Pvoyecto (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Cernea, Michael (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Robert Carlsen (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Bunge, Ruth Sombul (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Bolanos Margarita (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Linda Asturias (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Alonzo, Armando (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Misc. Corresp. G-P (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Miss. Corresp. S-W (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Brigittine French (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Class materials
    - Notecards and course outlines (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - B. Paul vita
    - For Tree: "Fourth World Philol" (doctoral proposal) (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Census Data (Box 10)
  - Field notes #101 - #1075 (Box 10)
  - Notes unfiled (Box 11)
  - Lectures (Box 11)
  - Field notes 111 – 197 (Box 12)
  - Field notes 301 – (Box 12)
  - Field notes 201- (Box 13)
  - Field notes 361- (Box 13)
  - Field notes 401- (Box 14)
  - Field notes 461- (Box 14)
  - Field notes 501-609 (Box 15)
  - Lectures (Box 15)
  - CC 1951 (Box 16)
  - Course notes (Box 16)
  - SR115 – course?/publication? (Box 17)
  - Lois Paul materials (Box 17)
  - Cultural notes (Box 18)
  - Lecture notes from classes taken (Box 19)
    - Language and Culture – Hoijer – Spring 1939 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Linguistics 228 – Hoijer - Winter 1938 (Dall's notes) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Phonetics 375 – Andrade – Autumn 1938 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Exotic Lang – Yucatec – Autumn 1939 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Linguistic Reading Notes (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Linguistic Analyses 385 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Comp. Sci. of Culture 211 – R.B – 1934 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Selections from my "Soc. Anth. Notes", made 11/21/48 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Soc. Anth. 240 – U of C Syll. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Method in Culture Anth. – B. Paul (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Nat. of Culture – Kroeber (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Folk-Soc'y 345 – Redfield – Spring 1939 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Maya, etc. 353 – Redfield – Summer 1939 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Paper for "Methods in Cultural Anthro.", Participant-observer tech. (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Bibliographies – Middle America (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Folk Society Notes (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Diary and supplements, June 1941 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Diary, Sept. 1941 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Folk Socy 345 – 3 papers – Spring 1939 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Interviewing (lecture material) (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Values (lecture material) (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Misc. to be filed (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Aq Pop Q (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous files dealing with Guatemala (Box 19)
    - Guat '64 Summer: receipt, lists (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Final Report – 1946 Guat. Project, La Alameda (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Rich Adams – AID project? Mitchell Seligson – Hinshaw proposal (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Lists and clippings, D Sq. (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Guat. News clippings and tables, (santos, etc.)1985 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Notes (unused) for D Sq (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Teresa Cumatz's tape and two color photos (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Tax – Shultz/Dam letters 1983, also Hinshaw: '76 quake report (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Rigoberto Monchu case 2/99 and "Truth" clippings (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Clancy's handwritten mss. (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - SP, Jan. 1978: Interviews – S,T,X,Y,Z, and miscellaneous, Proyecto and non-Proyecto. (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - SP, Jan. 1978: 1960 robbery documents (2), V-1, V-2 (ex-Merida), V-3, V-2 and V-3 comments (critics), Alinsky and Geiger. (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - SP Health Project, 1975-1978 (1 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - SP Health Project, 1975-1978 (2 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - SP Health Project, 1975-1978 (3 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - SP Health Project, Interviews A-C, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - SP Health Project, Interviews D-P, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - SP Health Project, Interview Quiacain and misc., 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Household Composition: Comparative Material (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Files related to bone setters (Box 19)
    - Bonesetters: various reprints (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Bonesetter shorter and lined tablet (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Bonesetter mss, copies 3, 4 and 5 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Bonesetter mss (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - San Pedro – Urbanization interviews, Summer 1974 (Box 20)
    Note: box 20 also includes slides of S. Pedro (1993), 10 notepads of notes, notecards, sound recording tape, 3 small boxes of slides, and a box of 12 audio tapes.
    - S. Pedro: Urbanization Interviews by Demarest, Juan Gz Puac Diary, Summer 1974. (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - S. Pedro: Urbanization Interviews by Demarest, Juan Gz Puac Diary, Summer 1974. (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence
    - Carmack Corresp. 1984-85 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Misc. Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - San Pedro Corresp. 1966 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Tapes
    - Teresa's tape transcript, orig. and copy (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous files - notes/clippings/papers/slides
    - Ms: Julian's conversation; Prot's growing threat (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - The Alcadia Revolt. Jan. 1996 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Publication Possibilities, Exped. Mag., U. of Iowa (Carren) (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Mss: Intro. Protestants, etc. 9/19/95 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Protestantism – Misc. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Clippings: education and religion (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Panaj. Lois, July 1969 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Travel plans and information 1962 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Misc. from Guat. (sorted 6/68) (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Misc. 12/73-3/74 (Panaj.) (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Religion – Misc. Notes 1941 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - 1964 clippings (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - 1965 notes II, copy 2 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Misc. from Caspar circa 1967 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - 1962 August copy 1 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - 1962 Augustin Escritos (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Extra copies of SP documents re: D. Sq. article (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Guate. Misc. documents 1983 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Relacion de Zpotitlan y Sachitepequez (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - "Extermination in Guatemala" 6/2/83, NY Review. (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Allan Nairn, "Guns of Guatemala" 4/11/83, N Republic (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - "Chiapas Revisited" April 1983, Inst. of Current World Affairs (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Embassy data, Jan. 1983 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Asilomar 4/84: Carmack, Dunbar, Pansini, Demarest (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Briggs, J.L. Role of Holy Spirit in Accult. 1962 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Miscellaneous files – trip in 1997?
    - San Pedro, Jan-Feb 1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Interviews 1997 (and correspondence) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Reprints (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence files, 1965, 1956
    - Correspondence: Misc. 1965 from Guat. (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence re: S.P. 1956 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Class files
    - Alfredo, Gomez Davis, Muralles, Dr. Chico Mz (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - SP Schools' Personnel – Zavala. Feb. 1994 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Peritos condadores, etc. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Chema: lists – including students, non-teacher peritos, nurses, new promocion, changes of position – 1994 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Chema's (new lists, 1995) (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Maestro lists (Chema) July-Aug 1995, Enrollment (spiral notebook, diary) (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Teacher lists and tallies (Chema Cox) (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Anth. 120, Primitive Curers, Aut. 1973 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Primitive Curers 130/330, Fall 1975 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Primitive Curers, Bib. etc, 1976 and before (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - The Experiment (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - 1965 visit
    - S. Pedro '65: Documents, notes, misc. ideas, tabulations, demographics (tabulations removed 8/76 to take to Guat.) (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Guat. Summer 1965 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Block maps
    - Maps (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Maps Block 21, 22 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Map Block 15 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Map Block 16, 17 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Map Block 20 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Maps Blocks 4, 5, 6 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Map Block 10 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Map Block 11 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Map Block 13, 14 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Map Block 9 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Map Block 1 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Map Block 7 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Maps Block 8, 12 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Maps – misc. prep. Material (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Maps Block Outlines (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Tables etc. selected from old misc. folder 8/76 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Map Block 18, 19 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Manzana 18 (1976) (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Block 18, S Pedro, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Manzana 17, Pablo Cox Bicxut (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Papers
    Note: box 21 also includes notecards re: shamans, faith, spirits, etc. and midwives, and one audio tape: "shamans, midwives, economic change" 1/24.93
    - Town map – orig. sketch (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Field notes Jan.-Mar. 1974 (Lois) and misc. Guat. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Recruitment, unused notes (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Misc. diary entries on social behaviors 1941 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Biog. Susana (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 3567-3633.2 Sex-Marriage II (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Aug. Diary copies 1941 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Diary 6/24-7/3 1956, Lopez-La Parroquia de San Pedro 1960, 6/25-6/30, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Diary 7/2-7/13 1962 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Diary 7/17-8/17 1962 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Diary 7/12-9/7 1964 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Diary 7/22-10/22 1965 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Diary 11/9-12/7 1965 plus misc. notes, Aug. 1968 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Itinerary and Diary, Ben and Lois, Dec. 1973 - Mar. 1974 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Typescript journal pages from Guatemala, 1941
    - Additional Papers: typescript journal pages from Guat. 1941 (Box 21, Folder 1)